[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[Apocalypse Log 6]
Where am I?
I'm okay.
Lie.
Are you feeling better?
Back to causing trouble already?
I just wanted to get some water.
Lin Zai.
Don't you know what you're allergic to?
How was I supposed to know
I'd be allergic to that fruit?
Besides, I didn't want to suffer like this.
Because of you, we've wasted a lot of time.
If you continue to defy me,
I guarantee you'll be the one
who suffers in the end.
So, now you think I'm a nuisance?
If you hadn't taken me away,
none of this would have happened.
Lin Zai.
I only need to ensure you're alive.
Don't force me to use
the methods I use on others...
on you.
It's not safe here.
We need to leave quickly.
That's a mutated zombie, right?
It's so huge. If we run into it,
not even a god could save us.
That's right. It's a Class A zombie.
Ordinary methods can't kill them.
Fine, tie me up if you want.
But what is this for?
To stop you from eating things
you shouldn't again.
I promise I won't.
Besides, I didn't get an allergy on purpose.
It hurts when you tie me like this.
Hey!
You're doing this for revenge, aren't you?
Do you think this will make me obedient?
We'll see about that.
What now?
What are you doing?
You don't want biscuits or meat?
I'd rather die than eat your food.
Lin Zai.
Are you treating my words as a joke?
Let go.
Do you enjoy being a dog that much?
Taming a dog that bites is simple.
You just have to pull out its fangs.
Lin Zai.
I'll say this one last time.
Eat properly.
This is the last time I'll indulge you.
I'll say it again.
My only job is to bring you back alive.
If you don't want to eat,
then I'll use my own methods to make you eat.
Are you planning to sit there all night?
It's so cold.
Why is there a draft everywhere?
You're not tying me up?
There's no need. You can't run away anyway.
Hey.
You're taking me back, and then what?
What will happen to me?
And what do you get out of it?
Don't ask questions you shouldn't.
Will I die?
You're the first immune
our organization has found.
What will you do to me?
You won't cut me open, will you?
That's not within my scope of duty.
When that day comes,
you won't care if I live or die, right?
You'll have to survive until then first.
Stay close to me.
I don't have a choice anyway.
Guang Qi.
I am here.
Do experiments on the zombie virus
cause harm to the immune body?
I'm sorry.
You do not have the authority
to query this question.
Lie.
Look.
This boar looks much tastier than a rabbit.
If we catch it,
it'll last us for several meals.
Lie, a zombie!
Ouch!
Wait, don't kill me! I'm human!
You weren't bitten by a zombie, were you?
No.
I disguised myself as a zombie to go hunting.
I haven't eaten in days.
I finally spotted a wild boar.
I'm sorry. I thought you were a zombie.
My friend didn't do it on purpose.
Your wound needs to be treated quickly.
Do you have a camp? We'll take you back.
Yes. My camp is nearby.
I'm counting on you.
This was a mistake on both our parts.
We can't just leave him here
to fend for himself.
Don't worry. It won't take much time.
Thank you.